Mummy ji Keshav ji
Mummy ji just now the baby said Papa
[screaming sound]
did he say Papa,
yes [laughter]
see Mummy ji I told you that in this world the
first person to say Papa is oh wow my
child said
Papa, my child said Papa, no no
Mummy ji I heard it myself, he
said Papa, if it is like this then make him
call again and show it right now
son said Papa, Papa said Papa, Papa said
Papa,
why is this?  [laughs]
Look, Mom, he said it.  She is still small, so only
pie is coming out.
Hey crazy girl, the voice is not coming from above but from below.
Mummy ji, whether the voice came from above or from
below.  It came from inside it, right?
[laughter]
You don't get good endings, Mom.